Guide to the Rice University Association of Rice Alumni records, 1922-2019 UA 003
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series VIII. Awards
  - Meritorious Service Award
    - Meritorious Service Award Recipients, 1986-2016; 164520
      - Ralph Noble '48, 1986; 164522 (Box 25, Folder 4)
      - Fred Stancliff '26, 1986; 164523 (Box 25, Folder 5)
      - Bill Ballew '40, 1987; 164524 (Box 25, Folder 6)
      - George R. Miner '50, 1987; 164525 (Box 25, Folder 7)
      - Russell Pitman '58, 1988; 164526 (Box 25, Folder 8)
      - Joseph F. Reilly, Jr. '48, 1988; 164527 (Box 25, Folder 9)
      - Ellen Elizardi Kelley '71, 1989; 164528 (Box 25, Folder 10)
      - Anette Gano Gragg '47, 1990; 164529 (Box 25, Folder 11)
      - Katherine Tsanoff Brown '38, 1990; 164530 (Box 25, Folder 12)
      - John Boles '65, 1991; 164531 (Box 25, Folder 13)
      - Willie May Chapman Cole '33, 1991; 164532 (Box 25, Folder 14)
      - Genevieve Pyle Denme '32, 1991; 164533 (Box 25, Folder 15)
      - Lawrence A. Hamilton '29, 1991; 164534 (Box 25, Folder 16)
      - Mary Lou Margrave, 1992; 164535 (Box 25, Folder 17)
      - Robert A. McKee '40, 1992; 164536 (Box 25, Folder 18)
      - William H. Merriman '67, 1992; 164537 (Box 25, Folder 19)
      - Paul E. Pfieffer '38, '48, '52, 1992; 164538 (Box 25, Folder 20)
      - Frank T. Abraham, 1993; 164539 (Box 25, Folder 21)
      - Earl Douglas Mitchell, 1993; 164540 (Box 25, Folder 22)
      - Pamela R. Smith '55 and Thomas D. Smith '51, 1993; 164541 (Box 25, Folder 23)
      - Linda burge Bramlett, 1994; 164542 (Box 25, Folder 24)
      - Marilyn Hellums, 1994; 164543 (Box 25, Folder 25)
      - Gus A. Schill, Jr. '55, 1994; 164544 (Box 25, Folder 26)
      - JD Bucky Allshouse '71, 1995; 164545 (Box 25, Folder 27)
      - James W. Hargrove '43, 1995; 164546 (Box 25, Folder 28)
      - Paula Meredith Mosle '52, '59, 1995; 164547 (Box 25, Folder 29)
      - Karen Hess Rogers '68, 1995; 164548 (Box 25, Folder 30)
      - Nancy Moore Eubank '55, 1996; 164549 (Box 25, Folder 31)
      - Neal Lacey, Jr. '52, 1996; 164550 (Box 25, Folder 32)
      - Carl M. MacDowell, 1996; 164551 (Box 25, Folder 33)
      - Milton McGinty, Sr. '27, 1996; 164552 (Box 25, Folder 34)
      - Lydia A. Asselin '79, 1997; 164553 (Box 25, Folder 35)
      - C. Sidney Burrus '57, 1997; 164554 (Box 25, Folder 36)
      - Walter D. Murphy '48, 1997; 164555 (Box 25, Folder 37)
      - Butler Perryman '39, 1997; 164556 (Box 25, Folder 38)
      - Katherine Fischer Drew '44, '45, 1998; 164557 (Box 25, Folder 39)
      - Mary McIntire '75, 1998; 164558 (Box 25, Folder 40)
      - Phil Peden '38, 1998; 164559 (Box 25, Folder 41)
      - Steve Shaper '58, 1998; 164560 (Box 25, Folder 42)
      - Cynthia Allhouse, 1999; 164561 (Box 25, Folder 43)
      - John Heard '40, 1999; 164562 (Box 25, Folder 44)
      - Ed Oppenheimer '35, 1999; 164563 (Box 25, Folder 45)
      - James A. Castaneda, 2000; 164564 (Box 25, Folder 46)
      - Geraldine Smith Priest '51, 2000; 164565 (Box 25, Folder 47)
      - William Martin, 2001; 164566 (Box 25, Folder 48)
      - Ronald L. Sass, 2001; 164567 (Box 25, Folder 49)
      - Barbara Willis, 2001; 164568 (Box 25, Folder 50)
      - Karen Ostrum George '77, '78, 2002; 164569 (Box 25, Folder 51)
      - David Minter, 2002; 164570 (Box 25, Folder 52)
      - Frank C. Shelden '48, 2002; 164571 (Box 25, Folder 53)
      - Texas B. Anderson '81, '85, 2003; 164572 (Box 25, Folder 54)
      - Anne Shamblin Baillio '62, 2003; 164573 (Box 25, Folder 55)
      - Isaac Dvoretzky '48, '50, '52, 2003; 164574 (Box 25, Folder 56)
      - Nancy L. Boothe, 2004; 164575 (Box 25, Folder 57)
      - Raymond D. Brochstein, 2004; 164576 (Box 25, Folder 58)
      - Carl E. Isgren, 2004; 164577 (Box 25, Folder 59)
      - Albert N. Kidd, 2004; 164578 (Box 25, Folder 60)
      - Susanne M. Glasscock '62, 2005; 164579 (Box 25, Folder 61)
      - Ann Patton Greene '71, 2005; 164580 (Box 25, Folder 62)
      - Thomas B. Greene III, '71, 2005; 164581 (Box 25, Folder 63)
      - J. Dennis Huston, 2005; 164582 (Box 25, Folder 64)
      - Jimmy Roton, Jr. '85, 2005; 164583 (Box 25, Folder 65)
      - Vicki W. Bretthauer '79, 2006; 164584 (Box 25, Folder 66)
      - Melvin Hildebrandt '55, '56, 2006; 164585 (Box 25, Folder 67)
      - Martha Lou Broussard '57, 2007; 164586 (Box 25, Folder 68)
      - Katherine B. Dobelman '46, 2007; 164587 (Box 25, Folder 69)
      - Cathryn Rodd Selman '78, 2007; 164588 (Box 25, Folder 70)
      - Richard O. Wilson '52, '56 and Mary Ellen Wilson '54, 2007; 164589 (Box 25, Folder 71)
      - Margaret Ann Mauk Barnett '55, 2008; 164590 (Box 25, Folder 72)
      - Hally Beth Walker Poindexter, 2008; 164591 (Box 25, Folder 73)
      - Dan C. Steiner '77, 2008; 164592 (Box 25, Folder 74)
      - Richard A. Tapia, 2008; 164593 (Box 25, Folder 75)
      - Teveia Barnes, 2009; 164594 (Box 25, Folder 76)
      - Kathleen S. Matthews, 2009; 164595 (Box 25, Folder 77)
      - Jeffrey Rose '77, 2009; 164596 (Box 25, Folder 78)
      - Richard Stoll, 2009; 164597 (Box 25, Folder 79)
      - Anne Chao '05, '09 and Albert Chao, 2010; 164598 (Box 25, Folder 80)
      - Gilbert "Doc C" Cuthbertson, 2010; 164599 (Box 25, Folder 81)
      - Charles Szalkowski '70, '71, 2010; 164600 (Box 25, Folder 82)
      - Phoebe Tudor and Bobby Tudor '82, 2010; 164601 (Box 25, Folder 83)
      - Janice Cornell Doty '60, 2011; 164602 (Box 25, Folder 84)
      - Robert B. Hord, Jr. '74, 2011; 164603 (Box 25, Folder 85)
      - Robert L. Patten, 2011; 164604 (Box 25, Folder 86)
      - L.E. Simmons, 2011; 164605 (Box 25, Folder 87)
      - Robert Taylor '74 and Amy Taylor, 2011; 164606 (Box 25, Folder 88)
      - Chandler Davidson, 2013; 215240 (Box 25, Folder 89)
      - Harry Gee '60, 2013; 215241 (Box 25, Folder 90)
      - Melissa Kean '96 '00, 2013; 215242 (Box 25, Folder 91)
      - Cindy Lindsay '73, 2013; 215232 (Box 25, Folder 92)
      - Tammy Taura '84, 2013; 215246 (Box 25, Folder 93)
      - Milton & Laurie Boniuk, 2014; 215239 (Box 25, Folder 94)
      - Stephen Klineberg, 2014; 215243 (Box 25, Folder 95)
      - Alan Shelby, 2014; 215244 (Box 25, Folder 96)
      - Kevin Gass '88, 2015 (Box 25, Folder 97)
      - Bruce & Mary Lou '55 Laubach, 2015 (Box 25, Folder 98)
      - Walter Widrig, 2015 (Box 25, Folder 99)
      - Mary Bixby, 2015; 215238 (Box 25, Folder 100)
      - Rose Sundin, 2015; 215245 (Box 25, Folder 101)
      - Terrence Gee '86, 2016 (Box 25, Folder 102)
      - Art Gottschalk, 2016 (Box 25, Folder 103)
      - Victor Lopez, 2016 (Box 25, Folder 104)
      - Walter McReynolds '65, 2016 (Box 25, Folder 105)
      - Rebecca Richards-Kortum [Restricted], 2016 (Box 25, Folder 106)
      - Robert Maxfield, 2016 (Box 25, Folder 107)
      - Neil "Sandy" Havens, 2016 (Box 25, Folder 108)
      - Judy Ley Allen, 2016 (Box 25, Folder 109)
      - Edward Cox, 2018 (Box 25, Folder 110)
      - John Hutchinson, 2018 (Box 25, Folder 111)
      - David Gibbs '71, 2018 (Box 25, Folder 112)
      - Suzanne Deal Booth, '77, 2019 (Box 25, Folder 113)
      - George Webb '88, '91, 2019 (Box 25, Folder 114)
      - John Jaggers, '73, '73, 2019 (Box 25, Folder 115)
      - Charley Landgraf, '75, 2019 (Box 25, Folder 116)
- Series IV: Addendum
  - Graduate Alumni Committee (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Alumni Groups (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - SOLAR (Society of Latino Alumni of Rice) 1/2 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - SOLAR (Society of Latino Alumni of Rice) 2/2 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Law Group (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Rice University Chinese Alumni Association (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Friends Groups (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - SRIA (Society of Rice Indian Alumni) (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - ARUBA (Association of Rice University Black Alumni) (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Houston Alumni Group (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Houston Young Alumni Group (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Dallas-Fort Worth Alumni Group (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Alumni Contributions (Confidential) (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Alumni College, 2003-2004 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Homecoming/Family Weekend Data, 2003-2004 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Alumni Surveys (1 of 2) (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Alumni Surveys (2 of 2) (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - President's Office Followup, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Job Positions and Candidates (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - ACT Survey Services (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Performance Enhancement Group, Ltd. (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Effect of Hurricane Rita on Rice Alumni Correspondence (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Alumni Trips, 1996-2004 (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - ARA President's File (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - ARA and MBNA Donations & Program Summaries (1/2) (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - ARA and MBNA Donations & Program Summaries (2/2) (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - Addendum to MBNA Contract Agreement (1/2) (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - Addendum to MBNA Contract Agreement (2/2) (Box 26, Folder 28)
  - Alumni Homecoming, 1997 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Alumni Homecoming, 1998 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Alumni Homecoming, 1999 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Alumni Homecoming, 2005 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Alumni Homecoming, 2004 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Legacy Admission Letters (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Admissions (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - President's Letter (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Presidential Visits, 1992-1993 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Presidential Visits, 1995-1996 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Rice Today Events, 1994-1995 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Presidential Visits and L.A., 1996-1997 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Presidential Visits, 1997-1998 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Presidents' Executive Luncheon (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Rice Self-Evaluation Program (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Alumni Directory (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Publishing Concepts (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Alumni Directory Notes, 1997 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Alumni Directory Notes, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Memorial Plaques (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - RMC - Memorial Plaques (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - Rice History Notes (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - Parking (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - Bellaire Historical Society Notes (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - Volunteering and Charity (Habitat for Humanity) 1/2 (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - Volunteering and Charity (Habitat for Humanity) 2/2 (Box 27, Folder 26)
  - RMC (Box 27, Folder 27)
  - Al Beerman Memorial Fund (Box 27, Folder 28)
  - Rice: The Next Century Campaign Public Kick-off Events (Box 27, Folder 29)
  - Enron Owls (Box 27, Folder 30)
  - Rice Alumni Clubs (Box 27, Folder 31)
  - California Alumni Group (Box 27, Folder 32)
  - Presidential Planning Survey (Box 27, Folder 33)
  - Marketing - Online (Box 27, Folder 34)
  - Web (PCI) Contract (Box 27, Folder 35)
  - Funding Account Numbers (Box 27, Folder 36)
  - The Alumni Portal (Box 27, Folder 37)
  - The Alumni Portal with Ecommerce (Box 27, Folder 38)
  - Harnessing the Power of the Web A Think Tank Focused on: The Alumni Portal and Career Networking, 1999-05-24 (Box 27, Folder 39)
  - Rice Self-Study Report Part II: The Role of Information Technology in the University, A Strategic Analysis, 1995 (Box 27, Folder 40)
  - Discussion with Rice University, 2000-07 (Box 27, Folder 41)
  - Nextera: Rice University's Alumni Web Site Proposal, 2000-08-30 (Box 27, Folder 42)
  - Sallyport Editorial Board (Box 27, Folder 43)
  - Web Strategy Committee (Box 27, Folder 44)
  - Online Alumni Connections: Website (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Online Alumni Connections: Portal (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Online Alumni Connections: Payment Processing (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Online Alumni Connections: Online Directory (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Online Alumni Connections: Volunteer Connections (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Online Alumni Connections: Career Centers (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Online Alumni Connections: Bulletin Boards, Online Communication, Email Forward (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Online Alumni Connections: Online Education (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Online Alumni Connections: Management (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Alumni Trustee - General (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Alumni Trustee - Elect (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - University - Diversity (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - University - Provost (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - University - Presidential Search (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - University - Alumni Trustee - Houston (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - University - Alumni Trustee - Out of Texas (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - University - Alumni Trustee - Texas (Not Houston) (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - University - Presidential Search (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - University - Inauguration, 2004 (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - Historical Notes/Alumni Statistics - Alumni Involvement (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - Historical Notes/Alumni Statistics - Outreach (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - Historical Notes/Alumni Statistics - Rice Facts (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - Historical Notes/Alumni Statistics - Outreach (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - Committee Files - Executive Committee, 2003 (Box 28, Folder 24)
  - Committee Files - University Standing Committees (1/3) (Box 28, Folder 25)
  - Committee Files - University Standing Committees (2/3) (Box 28, Folder 26)
  - Committee Files - University Standing Committees (3/3) (Box 28, Folder 27)
  - Campanile Alumni Notes (MELISSA), 1916-1969 (Box 28, Folder 28)
  - Association of Rice Alumni - ARA State Charter/Filing Fee (Box 28, Folder 29)
  - Association of Rice Alumni - Alumni Assoc. History (Box 28, Folder 30)
  - Association of Rice Alumni - Report of the Long-Range Planning Committee, 1990-03 (Box 28, Folder 31)
  - Association of Rice Alumni - New Look, 2003 (Box 28, Folder 32)
  - Association of Rice Alumni - Strategic Plans (Box 28, Folder 33)
  - Association of Rice Alumni - Annual Report, 1989-1990 (Box 28, Folder 34)
  - Core Group Beta Test - Initial Findings, 2001-12-13 (Box 28, Folder 35)
  - Rice Donor Relationship Strength Within the Robber Baron Peer Group (Box 28, Folder 36)
  - The Annual Fund at Rice University: Selected Concepts for New Annual Fund Program Initiatives Program Planning, 2002-06-11-2002-06-12 (Box 28, Folder 37)
  - Core Group Meeting, 2002-01-25 (Box 28, Folder 38)
  - Association of Rice Alumni - Budget Notes (Box 28, Folder 39)
  - Class Ring - Class Rings Notes and Memos, 1975-1990 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Class Rings - Ring Agreements, Spring 2015 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Class Rings - Balfour Materials (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Class Rings - Ring Committee (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Class Rings - Notes (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Class Rings - Balfour, Rice, Ring Mail Lists (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Class Rings - Rings, 2017 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Class Rings - Miscellaneous (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Millennium Training (Guide to Donations) (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Sallyportal Promotional Materials (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Recruiting Graduates - Young Alumni (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Recruiting Graduates - Future Alumni Committee Retreat (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Recruiting Graduates - Young Alumni, 2013 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Recruiting Graduates - Houston Young Alumni (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Recruiting Graduates - "Life After School Explained" (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Board of Governors Meeting - University Advancement Committee, 1996-03-12 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Board of Governors Committee Meeting, 1996-05 (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Board of Governors Meeting - University Advancement Committee, 1997-09-17 (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - Board of Governors Meeting - University Advancement Committee, 1998-03-25 (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - Board of Governors Meeting - University Advancement Committee, 1998-05-20 (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting - University Advancement Committee, 1998-10-07 (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting - University Advancement Committee, 1998-12-15 (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting - University Advancement Committee, 1999-03-24 (Box 29, Folder 23)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting - University Advancement Committee, 1999-05-19 (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - Regular Meeting of the Board of Trustees University Advancement Committee, 1999-09-15 (Box 29, Folder 25)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting, 1999-12-08-1999-12-09 (Box 29, Folder 26)
  - Convocation Scripts/Schedules, 1994-2002 (Box 29, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence Regarding Tuition Charging and Desegregation, 1963-1964 (Box 29, Folder 28)
  - By-Laws of Rice University (Box 29, Folder 29)
  - Association of Rice Alumni Ad-Hoc Review Committee (Box 29, Folder 30)
  - RMC Building Fund and Related Budgeting and Meeting Minutes (Box 29, Folder 31)
  - History of Alumni Tent (Box 29, Folder 32)
  - Trophy Case (Box 29, Folder 33)
  - Furniture and Artifacts (Box 29, Folder 34)
  - Office Location (Box 29, Folder 35)
  - MBNA, 1996-10-1997-12 (Box 29, Folder 36)
  - Credit Card Information/MBNA, 1996-09-12 (Box 29, Folder 37)
  - MBNA Royalty Notices (Box 29, Folder 38)
  - MBNA, 1998-01-1998-12 (Box 29, Folder 39)
  - MBNA, 1999-01-1999-12 (Box 29, Folder 40)
  - MBNA, 2000 (Box 29, Folder 41)
  - MBNA Royalty Reports (Box 29, Folder 42)
  - MBNA, 2002 (Box 29, Folder 43)
  - MBNA, 2001 (Box 29, Folder 44)
  - MBNA Contract, 2005 (Box 29, Folder 45)
  - MBNA Documents (Box 29, Folder 46)
  - Credit Card Complaints (Box 29, Folder 47)
  - Helpful Info (Box 29, Folder 48)
  - MBNA Additional Documents (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Web Design, 2003-2004 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - AllLearn Online Education Courses for Alumni (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Alumni Files: General (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Interesting Alumni (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Prominent Alumni (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Problem Alumni (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Homecoming, 1993 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Homecoming - Reunions, 1994 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Homecoming, 1995 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Homecoming, 1992 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Homecoming, 1996 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Trustee Briefing, 2003-2004 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Commencement Speech Guidelines (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Pamphlets and Press Touting Rice University (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Comparing Rice's Alumni Association with Peer Institutions (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Alumni Directory Notes (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - Hard Copy Directory (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - Shepherd School of Music Performance with CDs (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - Conference USA Strategic Plan, 2006-06-05 (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - Rice Annual Gifts: Reunion Giving, Volunteer Handbook, 2003 (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - Rice Annual Gifts: Reunion Giving, Volunteer Handbook, 2000-2001 (Box 30, Folder 22)
  - Association of Rice Alumni Meeting, 2004 (Box 30, Folder 23)
  - Zelenka: Six Chamber Sonatas (2 CDs) (Box 30, Folder 24)
  - International University Breman Image Clip (CD) (Box 30, Folder 25)
  - "Think Again," National Tour (DVD), 2001-2002 (Box 30, Folder 26)
  - International University Bremen: Image Clip (VHS) (Box 30, Folder 27)